Office of Communications and Marketing Records UA252
Tufts Archival Research Center
Office of Communications and Marketing Records
circa 1861 -- 2021
Tufts Archival Research Center
Office of Communications
Communications and Public Relations
UA252
57.2 Linear Feet
15 Digital Object(s)
2.35 Gigabytes
This collection contains the records of the Office of Communications and Marketing, including files about Tufts faculty and Trustees; published issues of and production materials for Tufts magazines; video recordings of Tufts events or events featuring members of the Tufts community; and public relations and publicity files about Tufts schools, buildings, events, people, issues, and groups.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Office of Communications and Marketing, 2018 -- 2022, accessions UA-2019-036, UA-2022-034, and UA-2023-026.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in seven series: Public Relations files; Trustees files; Photograph and publicity files; Publications; Faculty files; Videos; and 2022 accessions. Series and item titles for the first six series were provided by the Office of Communication and Marketing.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains files about Tufts faculty and Trustees compiled by the Office of Communications and Marketing, including photographs, newspaper clippings, correspondence, publications, event programs, press releases, personnel records, resumes and other biographical information, course materials and notes, research and project proposals and reports, obituaries, and other materials. This collection also contains published issues of and production materials for Tufts Medicine, Tufts Nutrition, and Tufts Dental magazines; VHS and beta tapes, CDs, and DVDs of Tufts events or events featuring members of the Tufts community; and public relations and publicity files about Tufts schools, buildings, events, people, issues, and groups, including photographs, newspaper clippings, publications, event programs, press releases, speeches, and other materials.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Communications and Marketing is a part of the division of University Relations and manages the image of and communications from the university. Though documentation suggests that a department with these responsibilities has existed since the 1920s, the first official reference to the office appears as "The Public Relations Office" in the President's Report for the 1946-1947 school year. Its main responsibility was originally managing the image of the university, faculty, and students in national and local media. It also had direct ties to the Tufts' Alumni Review, first acting as the magazine's original publisher, and then solely as a contributor to the "Class Notes" section after 1955.
Since its inception, the Office has changed its name several times. It was originally known as The Public Relations Office in 1946, and had shifted by the 1970s to be named The Office of Public Information. In 1979, it was consolidated with the Office of Publications to create the Office of Communications; ten years later, this was updated to the Office of Communications and Public Relations.
As of 2019, the Office comprises three departments: Public Relations, Editorial, and Marketing and Branding. The Public Relations Department manages external media sources, and tracks news coverage of the university. The Editorial Department manages eight university publications in both print and digital mediums, and additionally oversees an online gallery of images. The Marketing and Branding department maintains the university's visual identity, as well as all official university social media.
University history; Medford Campus; Boston Campus; University Relations; Curriculum and Instruction -- Faculty
- Public Relations files, 1964 -- 2015; UA252.001; 6 Linear Feet
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is open for research. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged in received order.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains files about Tufts-related people, buildings, events, and issues compiled by the Office of Communications and Marketing. Files include photographs, newspaper clippings, publications, event programs, press releases, and other materials.
  - TUSM Medicine, 2012-02-11 -- 2-13-09-09; UA252.001.001.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Open for research.
  - Mount Vernon Report, 2005; UA252.001.001.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - New Faculty 2005, 2005-08-30; UA252.001.001.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - New Yorker, 2005-10-25 -- 2006-06-12; UA252.001.001.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Occupational Health Risk Grant, 2005-05-31 -- 2006-01-24; UA252.001.001.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Orientation, 2009; UA252.001.001.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Peacase 2006, UA252.001.001.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - President, 2011-02 -- 2015-05-17; UA252.001.001.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Provost, 2012-06; UA252.001.001.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Public Relations, 2012-04-19 -- 2014-06-10; UA252.001.001.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Post Graduate Plans 1990, UA252.001.001.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Rankings 2005, 2005-08-19 -- 2005-08-23; UA252.001.001.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Rushdie, Salman, 2005-06-14 -- 2005-08-26; UA252.001.001.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Science Coalition Roundtable, 2006-02-15 -- 2006-03-20; UA252.001.001.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 2005 Senior Survey, 2005-09; UA252.001.001.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Senior Survey 2007, 2007-09-13; UA252.001.001.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Study Abroad, 2004 -- 2007-09-28; UA252.001.001.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Task Force Undergraduate, 2003-05; UA252.001.001.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Summer Session, 2012-03-25; UA252.001.001.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Task Force Postdoctoral, 2006-04-13; UA252.001.001.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - TCI Award 2005, 2004-07-01 -- 2005-05-11; UA252.001.001.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Talloires, 2005; UA252.001.001.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tisch, 2014-02-10 --2014-05-02; UA252.001.001.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - TCU Senate, 2006-04-25; UA252.001.001.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Tisch, 2014-02-19; UA252.001.001.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Tonight Show, 2005-10-18 --2005-10-19; UA252.001.001.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Topline Analyis, 2005-08-26; UA252.001.001.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Top 500 Universities 2006, UA252.001.001.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Transgender Housing, 2005-03-25; UA252.001.001.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Truman Scholarship, 2005-03-28; UA252.001.001.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Tufts Communications 2005, 2005-11-15; UA252.001.001.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Tufts University Self Study Report, 2003; UA252.001.001.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - University College, 2004-05-05; UA252.001.001.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - USA Today - 2006 All Stars, 2006-09 -- 2007; UA252.001.001.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Vice Provost, 2011-05; UA252.001.001.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - With the World In Mind, 2014; UA252.001.001.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - WSSS, 2004-10-15 -- 2005-02-27; UA252.001.001.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Word of Mouth Marketing, 2005-12-20; UA252.001.001.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - A New Era of Higher Education Community Relationships, 2005; UA252.001.001.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Annual Report, 1997-07-03 -- 2012-05-01; UA252.001.001.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Annual Report 2006-2007, UA252.001.001.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2012-03 -- 2013-09-12; UA252.001.001.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Beyond Boundaries Campaign, 2006-10-21 -- 2006-10-31; UA252.001.001.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Carnegie Community Engangement Submission, 2006-08 -- 2006-12-01; UA252.001.001.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Center for the Humanities at Tufts, 2012; UA252.001.001.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - CLIMB, 2004-08-13 -- 2005-02-15; UA252.001.001.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Code of Ethics Statement, 2005-12-14; UA252.001.001.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Compliance Training, 2006-01-30; UA252.001.001.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Confrences & Lectures, 2012-04-23; UA252.001.001.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Counselor Profiles, 2004-09-01 -- 2005-09-01; UA252.001.001.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Rankings 2006/Competition Rankings, 2004-04-29; UA252.001.001.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - College Rankings, 1999-08-05 -- 1999-09-29; UA252.001.001.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Comencement, 2010 -- 2013-05-19; UA252.001.001.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Community Language Bank, 2006-04-06 -- 2006-07-11; UA252.001.001.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Communications Benchmark Survey, 2003-12; UA252.001.001.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Connection Op-Ed April 2006, 2003-12-01; UA252.001.001.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Golden, Dan, 2004-08-25 -- 2006-07-28; UA252.001.001.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Dashboard, 2006; UA252.001.001.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Der Spiegel, 2004-12-01 -- 2005-03-10; UA252.001.001.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Diversity Center, 2004; UA252.001.001.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Executive VP Patricia Campbell, 2012-07-13 --2014-03-28; UA252.001.001.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Emmanuel's Gift, 2005-09-28; UA252.001.001.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Engineering, 2010-07 -- 2014-03-04; UA252.001.001.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Engineering Teacher of the Year, 2006-07-14; UA252.001.001.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Engineering Without Borders, 2004-10-20 -- 2005-08-01; UA252.001.001.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Entrepreneurs, 2006-06-21 -- 2006-06-23; UA252.001.001.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - EX College, 1964-09-18; UA252.001.001.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Experts, 2006-04-13; UA252.001.002.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Policies for External Media On Campus, 2005-10-18 -- 2006-01-12; UA252.001.002.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Awards, 2005-11-07; UA252.001.002.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - EPIIC, 2000-01-20 -- 2006-03-26; UA252.001.002.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - American Studies, 2005-09; UA252.001.002.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Anthropology, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.002.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Art History, 2005-09-20 -- 2005-09-23; UA252.001.002.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Biology, 2005-08-30 -- 2005-09-30; UA252.001.002.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - BSOT, 2005-09-22 -- 2005-09-26; UA252.001.002.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chemistry, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.002.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Child Development, 2005-08-18 -- 2005-08-19; UA252.001.002.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Classics, 2005-10-07; UA252.001.002.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Comparative Religions, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.002.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Drama & Dance, 2005-09-01 -- 2005-10-05; UA252.001.002.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Economics, 2005; UA252.001.002.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - English, 2005-09-26; UA252.001.002.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Geology, 2011-08-23; UA252.001.002.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - German, Russian, Asian Languages, 2005-09-22; UA252.001.002.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - History, 2005-08-31 -- 2005-09-23; UA252.001.002.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Humanities Grant 2006 V. Sullivan, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.002.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Higher Education Reports, 2006-02-21 -- 2006-03-20; UA252.001.002.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Mathematics, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.002.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Music, 2005-09-21; UA252.001.002.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Peace & Justice Studies, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.002.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Philosophy, 2005-09-20; UA252.001.002.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Political Science, 2005-08-24 -- 2005-10-21; UA252.001.002.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Romance Language, 2005-08-20 -- 2005-09-23; UA252.001.002.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Sociology, 2005-09-15; UA252.001.002.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - UEP, 2005-09-22; UA252.001.002.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Visual & Critiical Studies, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.002.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Tufts General 1990's, 1998-09-14 -- 2000-11-29; UA252.001.002.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Tufts General 2000, 1991-10 -- 2000-11-30; UA252.001.002.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Tufts General 2001, 2001-09-26 -- 2001-11-07; UA252.001.002.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Tufts General 2003, 2003-04-22; UA252.001.002.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Tufts in the News 2003, 2003-02-10 -- 2003-06-18; UA252.001.002.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Tufts General 2003 Clips, 2003-02-13; UA252.001.002.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Tufts General 2006 Clips, 2000-12-01; UA252.001.002.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Tufts General 2009, 2008; UA252.001.002.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - 150ANNIV--WEB, 1993 -- 2001-07-17; UA252.001.002.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - 150th Anniversary, 1998-10-02 -- 1999-02-01; UA252.001.002.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Admissions, 2003-01-31 -- 2009-09-02; UA252.001.002.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Admissions Statistics, 1999-08-30 -- 2000-08-28; UA252.001.002.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Advance System, 2003-01-15 -- 2010-04-14; UA252.001.002.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - A Capella, 1999-09-07; UA252.001.002.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Africana Center, 2007 -- 2008; UA252.001.002.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - AFGNES VARIS, 2000-12-04 -- 2000-12-12; UA252.001.002.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Alcohol Policy, 1998-09-16 -- 1999-01-06; UA252.001.002.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Animal Research, 1994-04-01 -- 1994-10-05; UA252.001.002.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Animal Reseach Committee, 1994-09-15 -- 1996-03-06; UA252.001.002.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Armed Robbery, 2001-12-05; UA252.001.002.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Arts and Sciences, 2010-03-26 -- 2010-03-31; UA252.001.002.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Athletics, 2001-11-21 -- 2001-11-26; UA252.001.002.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Awards, 2001-04-01 -- 2003-04-29; UA252.001.002.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Bacow Inaug./150th, 2002-04-19; UA252.001.002.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Baronian, John, 2003-02-07 -- 2003-02-12; UA252.001.002.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Barron's College Guide, 2002-10-07; UA252.001.002.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Biology, 2012; UA252.001.002.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Black Enterprise, 1999-03-01 -- 2004-11-16; UA252.001.002.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Black History, 1998-02-26 -- 1999-02-24; UA252.001.002.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Bolles Collection, 2001-11-06; UA252.001.002.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Boston School of Occ. Therapy, 1999 -- 2001-10-27; UA252.001.002.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Bosworth, 1998-07-09 -- 2000-07-13; UA252.001.002.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Brick Bottom, 2006-06-29 -- 2006-06-30; UA252.001.002.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Brown, Larry, 2000-05-04 -- 2000-06-28; UA252.001.002.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Budget 1998, 1998-05-06 -- 2002; UA252.001.002.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Business Expenses, 2004-04-13 -- 2005-10-27; UA252.001.002.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Campus Safety, 2005-09-13; UA252.001.002.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - CANVAS, 2007-01-24 -- 2007-01-28; UA252.001.002.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Capital Campaign, 1999-03-11 -- 1999-04-07; UA252.001.002.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Leonard Carmichael, 1987-09 -- 2008-09-09; UA252.001.002.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Center for Promise, 2005-12-01; UA252.001.002.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Centers, 2001; UA252.001.002.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Certificate Programs/Adult Learning, 1990-05; UA252.001.002.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Chemistry, 2002-01-18; UA252.001.002.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Child Development, 2001-01-17 -- 2007-07; UA252.001.002.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 2001; UA252.001.002.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Commencement Speeches, 1999-05-11 -- 1999-05-23; UA252.001.002.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Commencement 1999, 1999-04-23 -- 2000-05-19; UA252.001.002.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Commencement 2000, 2000-03-06 -- 2000-05-16; UA252.001.003.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Commencement 2001, 2001-05-20; UA252.001.003.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Commencement 2002, 2002-02-21 -- 2002-05-20; UA252.001.003.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Commencement 2003, 2003-05-18 -- 2003-05-20; UA252.001.003.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Commencement 2004, 2004-05-23; UA252.001.003.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Commencement 2005, 1998-06-14 -- 2005-04-27; UA252.001.003.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Commencement 2006, 2006-01-13 -- 2006-05-21; UA252.001.003.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Commencement 2007, 2007-05-20; UA252.001.003.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Commencement 2008, 2008-05-15 -- 2008-05-18; UA252.001.003.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Commencement 2009, 2009-05-14 -- 2009-05-17; UA252.001.003.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Communications--Bad, 2002-01-16 -- 2002-04-26; UA252.001.003.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Community Health, 2001-05; UA252.001.003.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Community Relations, 2001-12-14 -- 2005-11-01; UA252.001.003.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Community Day 2004, 2004-09-01 -- 2004-09-28; UA252.001.003.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Conservation Medicine, 1998-09-29 -- 1999-01-25; UA252.001.003.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Constitution Program, 2004-01-23; UA252.001.003.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Constitution if the US in Modern English, 2001; UA252.001.003.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Contingency Planning, 1999-02-10 -- 2000-10-10; UA252.001.003.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Cooke Foundation, 2007-01-04; UA252.001.003.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Crisis Management Co, 2009-09-29; UA252.001.003.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Cummings School, 2002-06 -- 2013-05-17; UA252.001.003.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - DC Archives, 2005-09-08; UA252.001.003.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Dame School Survey, 2005-11-17; UA252.001.003.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - DANKA, 2005-08-29; UA252.001.003.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Dental School, 2002; UA252.001.003.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Development, 1996-01-20 -- 1997-10-17; UA252.001.003.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Digital Archives, 1999-01-11 -- 2001; UA252.001.003.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Direct Loan, 2008-10-27; UA252.001.003.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Dibiaggio, 1999-03-12 -- 2001-05-30; UA252.001.003.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Diversity, 1998-11-06 -- 2002-02-15; UA252.001.003.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Dowling Hall, 2000-10-03 -- 2000-10-12; UA252.001.003.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Drama and Dance, 2001-09 -- 2002-11-25; UA252.001.003.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Drug Development Center, 1996 -- 1998-08-17; UA252.001.003.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Drylongso Award, 2002-01-25 -- 2002-03-03; UA252.001.004.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dump & Run, 2000-08-31; UA252.001.004.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Econ Advisory, 2001-12-17 -- 2001-12-18; UA252.001.004.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Economics, 2001-12-17; UA252.001.004.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Education-Teach 21C, 2002-01-04 -- 2002-07-29; UA252.001.004.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 02 Electricity Crisis, 2002-07-12 -- 2002-07-19; UA252.001.004.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - James Elliot, 1989-04-10 -- 2005-12-01; UA252.001.004.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Engineering, 2009 -- 2010-04; UA252.001.004.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Engineering, 1999 -- 2011-11-21; UA252.001.004.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - EPIIC, 2001-11-05 -- 2003-04-12; UA252.001.004.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - faculty Books, 2001-02-05; UA252.001.004.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Fares Center, 2003-02-20 -- 2007-01-26; UA252.001.004.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Int'l Media Cvrge., 2004-07-12 -- 2004-08-19; UA252.001.004.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - International Media Coverage Tufts and Peer Institutions, 2004-08-19; UA252.001.004.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Jamshed, 2001-11-25; UA252.001.004.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Interns, 2000-09-22 -- 2006; UA252.001.004.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Healy, Pat, 2003-07-24; UA252.001.004.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Hessey Bill, 2001-03-01; UA252.001.004.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - HGTV/LMNO, 2007-06-06; UA252.001.004.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - History of Tufts, 2001-04-10 -- 2001-07-30; UA252.001.004.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Housing, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.004.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - International, 1998 -- 2011; UA252.001.004.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - GLSEN, 2000 -- 2002-02-12; UA252.001.004.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Global Health Council, 2010-02-23 -- 2010-03-01; UA252.001.004.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Gordon Institute, 1998-07-30 -- 1999-03-18; UA252.001.004.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Gore. Al, 2002-01-25; UA252.001.004.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.004.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Harmony in the Age of Noise, 2008; UA252.001.004.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Bill Clinton, 2000-10-31 -- 2009-02-02; UA252.001.004.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Fares Center, 2000-11-02 -- 2010-10-15; UA252.001.004.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Filming/Photog., 1990 -- 2015; UA252.001.004.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Financial Aid, 2012-06-06 -- 2013; UA252.001.004.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Fulbright, 1998 -- 1999; UA252.001.004.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 4, Folder 33)